[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 17, "question": "You want to be a Brit, really, don't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 18, "answer": "I think it may happen someday.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kamala Harris"]}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "CC", "VBG", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "UH", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "Jodi, are you as offended as everybody else seems to be the president called an attorney general the best-looking in the country?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "You know, I see why this is not a great story for the president, because Kamala Harris is a brainy, up and coming politician and it is a little strange that her national introduction to the political stage is a discussion about whether or not it was OK for the president to call her pretty or not.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jodi"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "Would you feel equally affronted?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "It's not the same.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Different people in different situations.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "If he told lower ranking employees in his administration, for example, that they were good-looking but they happened to be men, would you feel that that was equally offensive?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "No, because that's not a barrier to men participating in the work force.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "I mean, there's feminism and there's feminism and then there's nonsense, isn't there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "I don't think it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", ":"], "qSentId": 112, "question": "That's a disgrace?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "HAIT: She needs and deserves to be judged on her merits and her qualifications, not to be --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["90 percent"]}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "VB", ",", ":", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "But, Piers, would you walk into an editorial meeting for your program and say to a female producer in front of everybody else, you look fantastic today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "I don't -- look, (a), I've got 90 percent female staff.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "But who cares?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "No, you're a very handsome man and that's completely out of bounds.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Michelle Obama"]}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "JJR", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "Jodi?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "-- we maybe parsing an even smaller matter, Piers, because this is literally one word out of place which is significant in part only because Michelle Obama is so careful in everything she says that it's very rare to hear her make any kind of gaffe whatsoever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 164, "question": "Jonathan, do you find it another disgraceful incident?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 165, "answer": "No, I would attach zero significance to that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 182, "question": "Senator Mitchell, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 183, "answer": "I'm fine.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitchell"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["South Korea", "South Korea"]}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "I mean, can you see a scenario where America would have to do something?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "Well, we are obligated by treaty, of course, with South Korea to defend if there is an attack upon South Korea.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Theodore Roosevelt"]}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "What is the more -- what is the consistent strategy you think that's most effective?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBR", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "RBS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "It's pretty hard to improve upon Theodore Roosevelt's statement that you should walk softly and carry a big stick.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "Uncle Jeremy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeremy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Are you going to have a beard in the \"Entourage\" movie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "''", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ari"]}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "And can you watch your language please?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "You'll always be Ari.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "TO", ":", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "How do you get away, even from your closest nearest and dearest, from being the great Ari Gold?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "JJS", ",", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "Well, you know what's funny is I -- is I came up with that sketch and, I just thought it was a really fun way to -- just to kind of send up the whole, you know, preconceived notion of it all, because, you know, before I had done that role, there was no reference to me being anyway near or like that character.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "I wanted you to -- I said, my exact words to you were, can you treat me like Lloyd?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "Have you met him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "I -- I have met him, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "Was he flattered or enraged?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "Well, I -- no, he certainly was not enraged.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 371, "question": "I mean, can I tell a story?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 372, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "What -- did you -- did you see the end of the \"Funny Or Die\" clip?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "``", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "''", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Where will it be, Mr. Selfridge?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "Right in the front of the store.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Selfridge"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Selfridge", "Harry"], "LOCATION": ["Chicago", "Chicago"]}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "JJ", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "``", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 425, "question": "How bad is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 426, "answer": "It -- well, I have no idea, because you know what's interesting is when I met with the producers for \"Mr. Selfridge,\" I said, Harry is from Chicago and there's a very hard Chicago accent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", ":", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "Do you go along with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "IVEN: I -- I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 502, "question": "Is it going to happen, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 503, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 507, "question": "I don't know, but do you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 508, "answer": "I -- you know, I feel like I'm the last to know, if that makes any sense.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 511, "question": "Can you give me a flicker of hope?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 512, "answer": "Well, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "Can he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "Not at all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "How much is Hollywood to blame in terms of the culture, the system, the way it builds up big stars and then maybe leaves them alone when they're on the skids?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RP", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 582, "question": "What would you say to them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 583, "answer": "Well -- I mean, definitely surround yourself with great people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "WRB", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 605, "question": "What do you make of the way the debate's gone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 606, "answer": "You know, it's been incredible how everything has shifted just I would say in the last year.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 610, "question": "Would you like to get married yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 611, "answer": "Oh, definitely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "JJ", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 638, "question": "What was the original purpose of this film?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 639, "answer": "Well, originally, the director and I just set out to go find one of the world's last undiscovered waves.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Geoff"]}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "JJ", ",", "CC", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 644, "question": "But how did you hear about this and what prompted you to get involved?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 645, "answer": "Well, Geoff and I were friends and I knew he had quite a few projects on the go as a producer, reality-based, and some in the spirits world.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "CC", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "IN", "NNS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "Are we talking about another Rwanda happening that we're just not really covering much?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "The size of it, I think, is difficult to determine and less important than the fact that there is a definite civil and political conflict there that needs attention.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Rwanda"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 668, "question": "So how are you going to get this hyped enough to really make a difference, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "RB", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 669, "answer": "Well, I think one of the things that we're going to try to do, which a lot of filmmakers that have low budgets try to do is really engage the community.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 693, "question": "Are you concerned about treading into the political arena like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 694, "answer": "Not -- not necessarily.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 699, "question": "What do you say to them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 700, "answer": "Well, I mean, I think we all, you know, the -- the human condition should be put at the fore because I think there's a ripple effect.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130405pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 727, "question": "Are you ready to get on the computers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 728, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]